Yo, what's good, boys? In this video,
I'm going to be showing you guys how I
made $15,000 trading meme coins today.
$15,000 is like around 200 soulish. I
was a little bit off. I made like 190
soul, but you guys must be thinking
like, "Oh my god, $50,000 is a huge
number." But no, it really isn't in meme
coins. There are a lot of people in my
call that made over a,000 soul today,
which is like 80 to 90k. So, you could
say that I'm underperforming, but also
obviously 15k is a great day in the
trenches. And for me personally, I'm
always looking to improve. But let's
dive straight into this video. I kind of
wanted to run through some of my trades
that I did today. I had three really
specific trades that I wanted to go
through. All of which were 100 soul P&L,
which is like 7Kish, and then another
P&L, which was like 4Kish, and then
another one which is 3K. I'm going to
just run you through those three trades,
make it super simple, sweet, and uh
yeah, just explain it in depth. First
off, I want to show you guys this my P&L
calendar for this month. I did pretty
mid in the beginning of the month. I did
3K, 3K, 2K. I had a really good day
making 16k and then right here I ended
up taking a vacation. I was on vacation
for 10 days. So this whole void right
here all vacation. I took like two
trades while I was on vacation which was
this right here and ended up being
profitable in it. Had 10 days off. I was
scared I was going to be washed but
ended up coming back to a $15,000 day
which is an amazing day for me. But
let's dive straight into it. I want I
kind of want to show you guys this tweet
that I made the other day. And this is
kind of just to like inspire you to show
you guys that like okay this really is
not that complicated. If you look right
here, made 8K on LeBron joining the
76ers. Everybody knows LeBron, as I said
in the tweet. The cool thing about
memecoins is that if you're familiar
with internet culture, you can trade
meme coins pretty [music] freaking
easily. You're literally able to make
thousands, like I said, in literal
seconds and minutes. If you guys want to
check out that tweet, check out that
tweet. But random narratives like that,
you know, things that you see on
scrolling on Tik Tok, Twitter, Instagram
reels, you're able to pick up up on it
super super quickly, especially if
you're doom scrolling all day. Like you
you see the [__] that I'm trading. Some
could say you even have an advantage.
But let's get straight into it. I'm
going to run you through my first trade
of the day, which was this coin called I
right here. It's called Bullseye. I'm
going to run you through my thought
process on it. First of all, right here,
as you can see, 118 soul. That's not how
much I actually put in right away. Let's
go to mine, flip it. I kind of bought,
sold, and then I rebought back all the
way back up there, but we'll get into
that in a second. To begin with, let's
explain the narrative real quick.
Bullseye is pretty much Anom. If you
guys don't know Anom, he is the largest
crypto influencer uh pretty much in the
game. He has his own memecoin right now
at about $250 million market cap. So, he
is a massive massive influence in the
scene. And he pretty much just made his
own launchpad where you can make meme
coins on. And so, he released a tweet,
yo, I dropped this new launchpad where
you can launch meme coins from.
Instantly, I wasn't even paying
attention. I was actually reading one of
my chats. Like, I'm live doing this
every single day. And then I see this
just spawn in. Go to $500,000 market cap
within this is the 1 second chart by the
way. 20 seconds it's already at 500K. If
you caught this early, which one of my
friends actually did, not my friend, but
this guy named Radiance. He bought all
the way down here at like 20K. Made over
I think $80,000 on this one trade alone.
So, one could say that's a great trade.
So, let's get straight into it.
Obviously, Anom [music] huge influence
in the scene already. Him dropping his
own launchpad is like massive massive
news. And so, right away I'm like, what?
this is his own launchpad. So, I kind of
like warmed up into it. I ended up
buying with around like 10 soul right
here just to like warm up into the
thing. I kind of wanted to research the
narrative more. And then I checked out
the launchpad that he made, which is the
website that you can launch the meme
coins from. This was actually the first
memecoin created on the website. And so,
automatically the first memecoin created
on the website is obviously going to be
one of the main runners for this
narrative since, you know, it's the
first one that came out on his
launchpad, which is like good lore, I
guess. And so I researched it more,
ended up buying more. 20-ish soul here.
I think I ended up being 27 soul deep
around right here. And instantly in my
head, you know, as soon as I take a
trade, I like to form a thesis or even
before I take the trade. In this type of
situation, you don't have a lot of time
to [music] think. You kind of just got
to act. And so as soon as I bought in, I
bought 10 soul here. Instantly, I'm
thinking, okay, what are the price
targets on this coin? I'm thinking, Anom
has a coin at 300 mil right now. There's
no way this isn't going 3 to 5 mil. I
think that's super fair. I think the
narrative's really, really good. I mean,
it's he's making his own Launchpad, kind
of [music] a competitor to Pump Fun. If
you don't know Pump Fun, Pump Fun is
where you launch coins on right now.
It's the main platform. So, he's
launching a competitor, I guess, to Pump
Fun in a way. And so, that's how I
really thought about it. Ended up buying
with 27 Soul here, which is around like
$2,000. Nothing crazy, you know. Just
got back from my trip. I didn't want to
I kind of wanted to warm up into the
trenches, but the trenches didn't want
me warmed up. They just wanted me there.
You know, trenches were just so [__]
hot today. I ended up taking a couple
clips here. My average entry was around
I think 600 or 700K. Yeah, 700K. Ended
up taking around like 15 soul here. So
pretty much like a little bit less than
Innies just to be a little bit safe. In
any's initials, like how much money I
put in. So I took out around 18 soul
here. Clipped out a bit more at 2.5 mil.
Let it chill and then around this 3 to 5
mil range. That's my price target.
That's where I really thought, okay, I
think this is going to hit 3 to 5 mil.
And so I kind of played it on the safe
side cuz I was up like 70ish soul here,
which is around like 5k. So I was like,
"Okay, first pretty much trade in like
10 days, you know, like maybe I should
maybe I should take some profits." So I
ended up taking some more there at 3
mil. Didn't end up taking any up here. I
probably should have took a little bit
at least like 5 to 10 up here. Ended up
taking more on the dip. Realistically, I
would have held this coin longer here.
But that is when this next coin Z500
comes in. I'm going to get into that in
a second. But as soon as I saw this Z500
coin come out instantly, I thought it
was the better coin. I thought it had
potential to flip this coin. And so I
actually ended up selling most of my
supply off, which I'm glad I did. I sold
eight soul here, another 11 soul there,
another 14 soul there. So I pretty much
exited my full position here and right
there I full clipped. So pretty much
fully out of that trade. Made 70ish soul
originally. Ended up rebying it later,
but we'll get into that after. Let's do
it in like sequence of events. And so
this coin Z500 comes out. It is like the
second coin or whatever dropped on his
launchpad or not the second coin, the
second good narrative that I saw drop on
his launchpad pretty much. Anom put out
a tweet around like 2 minutes, 5 minutes
after he announced the launchpad. you
know, he announced a launchpad here. And
then two minutes later, he ann he he
just put out an article and obviously an
article plus a launchpad. There's going
to be some type of like hidden clues to
a coin in there. Automatically, he's
feeding us the [__] narrative like
it's right in front of our face. Z500
and some he has a nickname in the
trenches. People call him Z. And so
instantly, that's like Z500, the first
onchain index. Anom index. You know, you
know how the S&P 500, we have the Anom
S&P 5, you know, you know what I'm
saying? Okay. And so he called it Z500
instit I'm like holy [__] this is a
really good narrative but in my head I'm
still like warming up into the trenches
like I just got back today so I'm not
trying to like put in a lot of money.
Obviously there's a lot of people that
bought before me but I don't want to
show you guys that cuz it'll just like
confuse you guys probably a little bit.
Coin instantly spawned in really high
cuz obviously the narrative is really
really good. And over here I was
considering you know does this have
potential? Like is Bullseye really this
good of a narrative? First of all it's
spelled wrong. It's Bulls's eye. So I
was like okay that's one factor. Second
of all, the Z500 is just a way better
narrative. If you pretty much if you go
on the actual physical website, it
literally says Z500, the first meme
index. So, in my head, I'm like, "Okay,
this is [snorts] definitely better." And
so, that's we'll go back a little bit.
That's why I sold all my stuff down
here. I had the thesis pretty early. I
had a 200k entry with around only eight
soul. 8 soul is only a couple hundred
bucks. I'm sad I had the thesis. I had
the vision. I was right, but I didn't
buy enough. But that's fine cuz I still
made around 50 soul on this trade. Once
again on this trade I ended up buying
more later on selling. So I'll show you
guys that after. But yeah, ended up
buying with seven sold down here. 200K
entry. I was up pretty much a 5x
already. I didn't sell anything at 1.5
mil because this one was still sitting
at 3.5 mil. So I thought it had
potential to double from 1.5. It
actually ended up doing that. I made a
call on the Pump Fun app. If you guys
don't follow me on the Pump Fun app,
follow me on there. I just started doing
call outs. It's a new feature they
implemented which you could pretty much
just post a thesis to a coin that you
like and then if you like the thesis you
could buy it. If not, fade it, whatever.
Gain conviction off the thesis,
whatever, you know. So, I posted the
thesis at around I think it was around 7
or 800K, right around this range, I'm
pretty sure. It was a little bit late
because it was my first time actually
using it, the callout feature. So, would
have called it instantly, but ended up
not doing it. So, let this ride out a
bit longer. You know, there was a huge
dip. I ended up holding through all of
it initially right here from at like 1.5
mil. I'm up like I'm up I'm up like a
3.5x 4x or something like that, you
know, nothing crazy. Like 30 40 soul
here probably. And so yeah, I genuinely
thought it would flip and it pretty much
did. At one point it went to 2 or 3 mil
here or I ended up selling some of my
supply here at 2.3 mil. You know, I saw
this one dumping pretty hard. It
actually ended up dumping to 1.3 and I
was like, "Okay, how long is this
narrative going to stay alive for?" You
know, um is it going to continue
battling each other to see who's the
winner? But if you guys don't know what
PVPs are, they're pretty much when two
coins battle each other and it's somehow
related to the same narrative. It's not
the same narrative, but you know, Ansom
Launchpad, two coins on Anom Launchpad,
which one's going to win, right? So,
ended up selling some more up here cuz I
didn't want to just stay in this PvP
forever. I sold a lot over here, and
I'll explain why in a second. I sold a
lot over here. I sold around 40 soul.
And you might be thinking, "Oh, you
thought you you thought it would flip,
right? Why are you selling 40 soul?" And
yes, you're right. Why would I be
selling 40 soul? If we go back here, I
ended up rebying here at around 2.4 mil.
And right here is literally why wallet
tracking is so important. If you guys
don't know Moonshot, they pretty much
list coins on their platform on their
app. And then that just gains more eyes
on the coin. So yeah, I tracked a wallet
that snipes whenever they list a coin.
So as soon as I saw a moonshot listing
instantly being put on within [music]
like 30 minutes of the coin being
released, I was like, "Oh [__] this
could be like cabal. Like they could
just run this one instead." I ended up
rebound here with another 50 sold at 2.5
mil because, you know, this one was
still at 2.2 and so I thought the volume
would switch back over and that's
exactly what it did. It ended up dumping
down to 1.2. I sold all my supply pretty
much over at 4 mil. You know, I did a
little scalp and right here I was just
up like a clean clean 100 soul or 80 or
90 soul and yeah, pretty much got full
out of that trade there. And so that's
why you guys see like 118 soul. I didn't
buy actually like I didn't hold that
much at once, you know. So yeah, that
was a pretty clean trade. I'm not even
going to show this part. This part's a
little complicated. Actually, [__] it. I
I'll explain this part. Pretty much
Anom. Pretty much if you end up burning
supply of this coin, which is around
$100,000, you gain like a little status
on the coin, which is called diamond.
Nobody's going to burn $100,000, right?
That's insane. And so, a trader actually
burned $100,000, and it was the first
coin to be verified as diamond. [music]
If you don't know what burned is, it
pretty much means like, okay, you have
$100,000, boom, it's gone, right? It
goes into the void, it's done, and then
the coin just is able to run smoother.
Whatever. I actually explained that in
my free course or not my free course, I
think it's my my paid course, like 100
bucks if you guys want to check that
out. But yeah, ended up buying 30 soul
here again. Sold 22 at 5 mil. You know,
a little scalp and then Anom obviously
interacted with it again and I sold all
of my supply at the top. Pretty much
overall great trade. Traded it pretty
well on this end. All right. Now, if you
go to this side, I didn't trade it as
well, the Z500, because, you know, it
was it the other coin was just pretty
much just like really cabal. Like they
really wanted the other one to run. And
so, that kind of [__] me up a little
bit. Ended up buying a lot here,
selling, buying, selling, and then I
rebought like 40 soul here. Boom, bada
boom, bada bang, bada boom, sold
everything. And then, yeah, ended up
taking a little bit of a loss there, but
it's okay cuz I still made $4,000 on
this one. And then $8,000 on this one,
right? two trades that I could have
made, you know, a lot a lot more money.
If you look at the top traders in this
coin, someone made 76K, 50K, 50K, 50K,
50K. So, guys, lock in ton of money to
be [__] made in meme coins.
Genuinely, if you guys are completely
new, check it out, bro. Just [__]
check it out, man. I'm telling you guys
right now, changed my life. Changed so
many other people's lives. But
obviously, it's a scary it's a it's not
scary game. It's a it's a risky game if
you're not going to give it your all. If
you do give it your all, I think within
a month, two months, maybe three months
of sitting there 10 hours a day, you can
make it. I truly believe that cuz that's
exactly what I did. But yeah, let's go
on to the next narrative. But before
that, I just want to mention that with
all this volume that I did right here,
118 soul sell, 220 soul sell, I'm
actually getting a ton of cash back. I'm
actually getting a ton of cash back
because I'm trading on terminal. If you
look here, I actually made like 15 soul
today alone just on cash back. And
that's because Terminal has the best
cash back on your trades. And what that
means is that if you trade a lot and you
create volume by buying or selling, you
basically get money back on your trade
from the fees that you generate, right?
So, Terminal has the best freaking cash
back out there. You're not going to find
anything better. So, yeah, check it out
in the description if you're not using
it already. Let's go into this next
trade. Now, now you guys might be
thinking if you're new to the trenches
that these two narratives were a little
complicated. I hope I did pretty good to
explain that. But this next one is
actually extremely extremely simple.
Something that you guys can all pretty
much read instantly. And I pretty much
read it instantly as well. I was one of
the first transactions to this coin. I
bought it at 4.45K market cap. It went
all the way to 75K. Did this all on live
by the way. I explained my whole thought
process through the entire thing um on
Twitch.tv/bag
#ad. No troll. But pretty much the
narrative for this coin was meme. We
accidentally became a meme. Netflix
actually released today that they're
dropping a duck a series called we
accidentally became a meme. If you go to
the Netflix titles, it's literally it
dropped today. It's just a bunch of
episodes on how famous memes like, you
know, Neon Cat. I don't know if you guys
have seen this one. It's like a super
famous meme. Might have seen it around
somewhere, but pretty [clears throat]
much backstories on how memes just got
created, right? And obviously that's
just a [__] generational narrative.
Easy bond. At least bonding is like 30k.
It at least deserves 30 to 50k in my
head. I was like, listen, we're trading
meme coins. They're explaining how their
memecoin got created and they made a
whole series for it. In my opinion, it
deserved higher, but ended up
identifying this narrative super early.
Called in my VC. We all, I think,
printed. I'm not sure. Actually, I think
they actually faded me on this one,
which uh yeah, screw you guys if you're
listening. I only ended up buying three
soul, which is a couple hundred bucks.
Yeah, I think like 200 bucks, 300 bucks,
whatever. Bought a little bit down
there. Didn't sell anything till about,
let's see here. I didn't sell anything
till about right here. Oh, actually, no.
I sold a bit right here. Actually, sold
three, saw at 16K, another three,
another two. So, I already sold like 9
soul, which is already a 3x. I'm out for
a 3x pretty much. I let the rest ride. I
had like five soul remaining here.
Clipped a little bit more up here.
Another two soul. And then I actually
ended up rebying over here. Another
three soul because once again, guys,
you're able to capitalize on vamps. You
know, you might think vamps are scary,
this that, but sometimes they could
actually benefit you and you could
actually end up, if you really like a
narrative, you could actually end up
buying more supply if you are right
about the coin. And in this case, I was
right. They tried PvPing the same
narrative, which means battling the same
narrative with something different.
Instead of we accidentally became a
meme, it was I accidentally became a
meme. And the reason for that was
because in the videos, all of them are
titled I accidentally became a meme. I
accidentally became a meme. Right?
They're all titled that. But the actual
series was called We Accidentally Became
a Meme, right? The whole series was
called We Accidentally Became a Meme.
And so instantly I was like, "Okay,
that's a weak vamp. That's not going to
vamp." So, I ended up buying three more
soul up here at 38K. You know, it's
nothing insane, but I just wanted to get
squeeze out a bit more profits. Sold
some up here. Sold another five soul up
there. I sold pretty much everything.
Oh, right here. Okay. Yeah. Got full out
of the trade. Made around $1,200 on
this. And then, yeah, that pretty much
wrapped up the entire day. I made a
bunch of smaller trades that ended up
getting me to 190 soul on the day plus
14.5K. Overall, was a WS day. There's
definitely a lot I could have done
better. There's people that made five
times what I made today, which is
honestly insane, but not really if you
think about it. Not even five times,
like eight times, 10 times what I made
today. So, yeah, just to show you guys
that there is no limit to how much you
can really make trading meme coins, you
know? You're going to start you're going
to start small. You're going to start
with like $5 profit, $10 profit, then
100, then 200, a,000, then boom, you're
up there, you know? So, it's a process.
If you want it bad enough, you just got
to [__] try it. I have a bunch of
entrylevel videos. If you go to my
description, it's in my w all for free.
I have like eight videos how to set up
everything. And then yeah, if you enjoy
those videos, I have another thing
that's a paid full walkthrough on how to
trade meme coins. It's literally only a
h 100 bucks. It's the price of two
[__] meals if you go outside your
house. So, I'd say it's way worth it
because I mean 100 bucks. I just made
[__] 15k today. You know, it's a
small comparison. It's a small price.
You know, if you're going out with your
friends, [__] it. Skip that one night
and then boom. But yeah, check out
Terminal in the description. It is the
best trading platform you guys can be
on. If you guys enjoyed this video, like
and then comment down below what you
guys want to see more of and if you
enjoyed this video. So yeah, check out
all the links in the description if
you're interested. I will catch you guys
in the next one. Thank you so much for
watching. Peace out, boys.